

Diogo Redin

Profile

I'm Diogo Redin, a front-end developer, currently studying Computer Engineering at Instituto Superior Técnico. Although I also like back-end development, front-end captivates me more because I can be closer to the experience end-users have.

Internships

Intern - Scientific Initiation Grant at M-ITI, Funchal, Madeira

June 2017 - September 2017

Designed an interactive platform to visualize tourist movements. Developed with HTML, CSS, jQuery, SVGs, D3.js and Node.js. The project resulted in a paper that was presented at SustainIT 2017 and won the best demonstration award.

Employment History

Customer Support at MediaLayout UK, Remote

February 2015 - October 2015

Responsible for providing customer support to 10+ different WordPress Themes sold on ThemeForest. Work was done part-time for a digital media agency.

Freelancer (Self-Employed), Remote

February 2011 - February 2015

Developed websites and premium themes for WordPress and Shopify. Themes were sold on ThemeForest, MojoMarketplaces and CreativeMarket. 6 products with a total of 440 sales. One of the WordPress projects I developed was featured on the 192th Issue of the Web Designer Magazine.

Students' association president at ESLFB

April 2014 - June 2014

Education

Bachelor's Degree Computer Engineering, Instituto Superior Técnico, Lisbon

September 2015 - July 2019

Enjoyed the most: Human-Machine Interfaces (18/20), Computer Graphics (14/20), Artificial Intelligence (16/20) and Management (16/20).

Extra-curricular activities

Startup Experience Assistant at Web Summit 2016

Courses

Introduction to React. js, XpandIT

Details

+351912043644

me@diogoredin.com

Date / Place of birth

1996-01-19

Lisbon

Nationality

Portuguese

Links

Portfolio Github

Languages

English

Portuguese